{
    "id": "8d87250dfa6e4dfcae47204ec11290e8",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am looking …………………… my keys.",
            "description": "To look for something is to search for it. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d007f3108d643d78247565499749257"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t agree …………………….. you.",
            "description": "We agree with a person, opinion or policy.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "963847ac1fb648fa9e5dfd2bcaaa56ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot count …………………… him.",
            "description": "To count on somebody is to trust them.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "29bcbdc2b0cd4748a9f31328be1cc462"
        },
        {
            "question": "He belongs …………………… a warrior clan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0e8982e8ad48452fba21164295383a04"
        },
        {
            "question": "They took him to hospital after he complained …………………… uneasiness.",
            "description": "You complain of a problem.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "about",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83e2f3942c9340a88eca7c2680514ef8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is still dependent ………………………. his parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63487163a9c54238aa2d32acb31126b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the eldest ……………………… the four siblings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e71e64287a534bcd9ec270e9ef0d1a43"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was amazed ……………………… her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d6c844cc70274d8b9883926ab7a820e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good ……………………. solving puzzles.",
            "description": "We say good at, bad at, poor at etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a5e6ebd401f44c9bc4405ad4a807d0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience were enthralled ………………………. the spectacular performance of the children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d2c118f9b70545c58078e8cf625bff4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ………………………. me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed3cfdcaf3cd4e14adb61f580749f41e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn't seem perturbed ............................... the commotion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e0fe08c20c764af8a7a09f25b3f313da"
        }
    ]
}